-抱歉 -天啊,我受够了
-I'm sorry! -That is it!
你不敲门就闯进来?
You barge in here and you don't knock?
-难道你不尊重别人的隐私权? -不,你慢着
You have no respect for privacy. No,you wait!
-我能说一件事吗? -什么事?
-Can I just say one thing? -What?!
这块布编的非常松,我仍能看见…
That's a relatively open weave. I can still see...
…你的胸脯
...your nippular areas.
六人行 第1季 第13集 看胸脯
The One With The Boobies
亲爱的,告诉他们你的病人
Honey,tell them the story about your patient...
如何把事想成另一件事
...who thinks things are other things.
例如电话响时她就去洗澡
When the phone rings and she takes a shower.
差不多是那样
That's pretty much it.
-但你说得很好 -谢谢
-But you tell it really well,sweetie. -Thanks. Okay.
快走开我们才能谈你
Now go away so we can talk about you.
好吧,我会想念你的
Okay. I'll miss you.
-他很不错吧 -他好帅,也好像很喜欢你
-lsn't he great? -He's cute. He likes you so much.
我知道,他人很好,而且很复杂
I know. He's so sweet. And so complicated,you know?
有点神经质,但又不是太神经质
And for a shrink,he's not too shrinky.
他会在沙发上做吗?
Think you'll do it on his couch?
我不知道…那有点奇怪
I don't know. That's a little weird.
沙发可是聚乙稀做的
It's vinyl.
大家还想要别的吗?
Okay,you guys want anything else?
-要,我要… -抱歉,卖完了,其他人呢?
-Could I have? -We're all out. Anybody else?
我是否错过某事?
Did I miss something?
她很生气因为我看见她的胸脯
No,she's still upset because I saw her boobies.
你看她的胸脯干吗?
What were you doing seeing her boobies?
那是意外,我可不是隔条街用望远镜偷看
It was an accident. I wasn't across the street with a telescope.
能换个话题吗?
Can we change the subject,please?
没错,因为那不是她的胸脯 而是她的胸部
These aren't her "boobies." These are her breasts.
菲比,我要的不只是改变字眼
Pheebs,I was hoping for more of a change.
我向来喜欢“波涛汹涌”
I always liked "Bazoombas."
给它个拉丁旋转拼写
Gives them a Latin spin.
我们放下这个不说了,好不好?
Can we drop this already,please?
你为什么要难为情呢? 它们确实是非常好看的胸脯
Why are you embarrassed? They were very nice boobies.
“好看”?它们很“好看”?
"Nice"? They were "nice"?
就这样?手套也很好看啊
That's it? I mean,mittens are "nice."
我…好尴尬
Okay. Rock,hard place. Me.
你真逗
You're so funny!
他真的很逗
He's really funny.
他不开玩笑的时候,我也不想待在这儿
I wouldn't wanna be there when the laughter stops.
等等,回去上句
Whoa,back up there,sparky.
那是什么意思?
What did you mean by that?
你似乎有亲密上的问题
It seems that maybe you have intimacy issues...
你用你的幽默和人保持距离
...that you use your humor to keep people at a distance.
我才刚认识你,我从亚当那里没听说过你
I mean,I just met you. I don't know you from Adam.
独子对吧?
Only child,right?
父母在你青春期前离婚?
Parents divorced before you hit puberty.
-你怎会知道? -你很典型
-How did you know that? -It's textbook.
各位,你们都认识我爸吧?
Hey,you guys. You all know my dad,right?
-打算在纽约待多久? -就几天.我在市中心有工作
-How long are you in the city? -Two days. I got a job.
我想和乔伊同住
I'm better off staying with Joey...
比来回坐渡轮好
...than going back and forth on the ferry.
-我没见过他 -他是我朋友罗杰
-I don't know this one. -This is my friend Roger.
-幸会,罗杰 -彼此彼此
-Good to meet you. -You too.
-玩布偶的那个怎么了? -爸
-What happened to the puppet guy? -Dad.
抱歉。罗斯,你的太太还好吗?
Oh,excuse me. So,Ross,how's the wife?
0比2了对吧?
0 for 2,huh?
钱德,说点好笑的
Chandler,say something funny.
我得挂电话了,我也想你
I gotta go. Miss you too.
-我爱你,但现在很晚了 -让我向她打声招呼，妈妈
-I love you,but it's getting late -Say hi. Hey,Ma.
我和包西达大夫约了时间
I made the appointment with Dr. Bassida and
什么?
Excuse me?
你知道这不是妈吗吧?
Did you know this isn't Ma?
她叫罗妮
Her name's Ronni.
宠物殡葬业者
She's a pet mortician.
当然
Sure.
你和她多久了…
So,how long you been...?
记得小时候我常带你去海军军港看大船吗?
Remember when you were a kid,I'd take you to the navy yard?
-从那时候就开始了? -不,才6年
-Since then? -No,it's only been six years.
我只想勾起你美好的回忆 让你不会觉得我一直是个大烂人
I wanted you to think of a nice memory so you'd know I'm not a terrible guy.
-你在干嘛? -切大蒜
-What are you doing? -Chopping garlic.
你不把他们压碎吗?
You don't crush it?
这是你的风格,我一向都是切的 真是个古怪的世界
You're having an affair,I chop garlic. It's a wacky world.
乔伊,你爱过吗?
Joe,you ever been in love?
-我不知道 -那就是没有
-I don't know. -Then you haven't.
-你的蕃茄烧焦了 -别想转移话题
-You're burning tomatoes. -You're one to talk.
你老爸爱得无法自拔 最糟的是我爱两个女人
Your dad's in love. The worst part is,it's with two different women.
拜托你告诉我其中一个是妈
Oh,man! Please tell me one of them is Ma.
当然其中一个是你妈,你是怎么搞的?
Of course one of them's Ma. What's the matter with you?
这就像你某天起床突然发现
It's like if you woke up and found out...
你爸是个双面人
...your dad leads this double life.
就像是为中情局工作的间谍
He's like actually some spy working for the ClA.
那一定很酷
That'd be cool.
但这个很烂
This blows!
你认为爸爸会骗人吗?
Do you think Dad cheated?
我没有这么想过.那一定包括了性是不是
I don't think so. That would involve sex.
我更加趋向于认为我们父母都不会做
I'd like to think that our parents don't do that.
为何父母就不能是父母?
I know. Why can't parents just stay parents?
为何他们就得成为人间男女? 为何他们要?
Why do they have to become people? Why do they have?
为什么…
Why...
…别再盯着我的胸部看
...can't you stop staring at my breasts?
什么?
What?
那一天你还看得不够吗?
Didn't you get a good enough look?
我们都已是成年人 此事只有一个解决之道
We're all adults here. There's only one way to resolve this.
既然你看过她的胸脯 你应该让她看你的小弟弟
Since you saw her boobies you have to show her your pee-pee.
知道吗，这事儿不会发生的
You know,I don't see that happening.
拜托,他说得对.以牙还牙
Come on. He's right. Tit for tat.
我不会让你看我的“牙”的
Well,I'm not showing you my tat!
-是菲比 -还有罗杰!
-It's Phoebe. -And Rog!
快上来
Come on up.
这下可好,罗杰来了
Oh,good! Rog is here.
-罗杰有什么不对劲吗? -没什么,小事.我讨厌这家伙
-What's the matter with Rog? -It's a little thing. I hate that guy!
为什么?因为他太善于分析 他就是这种人别这样嘛
So he was a little analytical. That's what he does.
他没那么糟
Come on,he's not that bad.
你错了!如果当初我感觉到
You're wrong! Why would I marry her...
她是女同志我何必和她结婚呢?
...if I thought that she was a lesbian?
我不知道,或许你想让婚姻失败
I don't know. Maybe you wanted your marriage to fail.
为什么?我为什么这样?为什么?
Why? Why would l? Why?
我不知道,或许自信心不足
I don't know. Maybe low self-esteem?
或许是弥补你让你妹相形见绌的愧疚
Maybe to compensate for overshadowing a sibling. Maybe
或许…等等,回到妹妹的话题
Wait! Go back to that "sibling" thing.
什么?我不知道
Well,I don't know.
你要使你的婚姻触礁
You could've sabotaged your marriage...
让你妹在父母面前不那么失败
...so the sibling would feel like less of a failure.
这太荒谬了 她不争气我并未感到自责
That's ridiculous! I don't feel guilty for her failures.
-你认为我不争气? -他不错吧
-You think I'm a failure? -lsn't he good?
我不是那个意思
Yeah. No,that's not what I was saying.
多年来我以为你支持我
I thought you were on my side.
但或许你婚姻失败目的是想巴结爸妈 让他们更心疼你
But maybe you sucked up to them so they'd favor you.
我娶女同志是想让你建立自信
I married a lesbian to make you look good!
你说得对.我的意思是,你说得对
You're right. I mean,you're right.
那不是威宝玩具的问题 而是威宝游乐宫
It wasn't just the Weebles,but the Weeble Play Palace...
和威宝游轮的问题
...and the Weeble's Cruise Ship...
它上面的救生艇让威宝能缓缓驶出
...with this lifeboat for the Weebles to wobble in.
偏偏妈妈把他们都给出去了
And Mom just gave them all away.
那滋味不好受
That's tough,tough stuff.
菲比,如果想看电影我们现在该走了
Pheebs,we're gonna catch that movie,we gotta go.
-打起精神来,瑞秋 -菲比,我们快来不及了
-Feel better. -We're gonna be late,sweetie.
-谢谢你做的一切,莫妮卡 -不客气
-Thanks for everything,Mon. -No problem.
各位,很高兴和各位再度见面
Listen,it was great seeing you again.
莫妮卡,饼干别吃太多
Mon,easy on those cookies,okay?
切记,那只是食物,不是爱
Remember,they're just food,they're not love.
我讨厌这家伙
I hate that guy!
晚安,各位
Good night,you guys.
这是我们订的女人
Oh,look. It's the woman we ordered.
需要帮忙吗?
Hey,can we help you?
不用,谢谢,我在等乔伊崔比亚尼
No,thanks. I'm just waiting for Joey Tribbiani.
我就是乔伊崔比亚尼
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
不是你,是老乔伊,天啊
Oh,no,not you. Big Joey. Oh,my God!
你比照片上帅多了
You're so much cuter than your pictures.
我是罗妮
I'm Ronni.
想吃起司(夹子)吗?
Cheese Nip?
乔伊有“栓子”,我要个“夹子”
Joey's having an embolism,but I'd go for a nip.
大部份人在宠物过世后
Most people,when their pets pass on...
希望它们就像睡着一样
...want them like they're sleeping.
但有些人要他们摆出姿势
Occasionally you get a person who wants them in a pose.
像追自己的尾巴
Like chasing their tail.
跳起接住飞盘
Or jumping to catch a Frisbee.
乔伊,如果我先走 我的姿势要像找钥匙一样
Joey,if I go first,I wanna be looking for my keys.
-这姿势不错! -嗨!
-That's a good one! -Hey.
嗨,爸爸.罗妮来了
Hey,Dad. Ronni's here.
-嗨 -嘿
-Hi. -Hey.
宝贝,你来干什么?
Hello,babe! What are you doing here?
你的假发留在我的住处
Oh,you left your hair at my place.
我想你明天用得上
I thought you'd need it tomorrow.
谢谢
Thank you.
谁想玩“扑通”游戏?
So,who's up for a big game of Kerplunk?
我不该来这儿
Look,I shouldn't have come.
我该走了,我不想错过最后一班地铁
I better go. I'll miss the train.
-不,我不要你坐这么晚的车 -我要住哪儿?这里?
-I don't want you taking that thing. -Where do I stay? Here?
我们去住饭店
We'll go to a hotel.
-不行 -不行
-No,you won't. -No,we won't.
你们去饭店就一定会办事
If you go to a hotel,you'll be doing stuff.
我要你们待在这儿,这样我就可以监视
I want you here so I can keep an eye on you.
-你要监视我们 -没错
-You're gonna keep an eye on us? -Right.
只要住在我家
As long as you are under my roof...
―切就得听我的
...you're gonna live by my rules.
那就是不准你们睡在一起
That means no sleeping with your girlfriend.
他好严格
Wow,he's strict.
爸,你睡我房间 罗妮,你睡钱德的房间
Dad,you'll be in my room. You can stay in Chandler's room.
那钱德呢?
And Chandler will be?
在这和我一起,轮船铺位
Out here with me,bunking up.
轮船铺位.如果闻到烟味 不要拉警报哦
Oh,bunking up. If you smell s'mores,don't be alarmed.
谢谢,你真是个好孩子
Thanks. You're a good kid.
我带你去看我房间
I'll show you to my room.
感觉真奇怪 你没说“不,谢了,时候不早了”
That sounds weird not followed by,"No,it's late."
只有今晚,明天你们就得做出改变
This is just for tonight. Tomorrow you gotta change.
改变?
Change?
-和罗妮分手 -我不能!
-Break up with Ronni -I can't!
不然就是向妈自首,这样是不对的
Then come clean with Ma! This is not right!
对,但是…我不想听,快进我房里
I don't wanna hear it! Now go to my room!
别踢了
Hey,kickie!
-你在干什么? -找寻舒适的位置
-What are you doing? -Getting comfortable.
-穿着内裤我睡不着 -你非穿不可
-I can't sleep in my underwear. -Well,you're gonna.
我一直在想… 我看见女人叠在女人上面会怎样
I was thinking about how I'm always seeing girls on top of girls....
她们是首尾相接,还是像煎饼一样叠起来
Are they end-to-end,or tall,like pancakes?
懂我意思吗? 我总想像自己和所有这些女人约会
You know,how I date all these women.
因为我总想梦中情人出现时
I always figured,when the right one comes along...
我就会勇往直前,坚持到最后
... I'll be able to go the distance.
但如今看见我爸…看起来
Now I'm looking at my dad,thinking
你不是他,你是你自己
You're not him,you're you.
当全天下都希望你继承你爸的事业时 你有屈服吗?
When they wanted you in your father's business,did you cave?
-没有.-没有
-No. -No.
你决心从事没有工作的演员事业
You chose the out-of-work-actor business.
这不是一件容易的事,但你办到了
That wasn't easy,but you did it.
我也相信梦中情人出现时
I believe when the right woman comes along...
你会有勇气对她说“不用了，谢谢,我已婚”
...you'll have the guts to say,"No,thanks,I'm married."
-你真的这样认为? -真的
-You really think so? -Yeah,I really do.
-谢谢,钱德 -滚开
-Thanks,Chandler. -Get off!
-嗨 -有事吗?
-Hi. -Hi. May I help you?
乔伊说我能用你的浴室 因为钱德正在用我们的
Joey said I could use your shower since Chandler's in ours.
好的.你是谁?
Okay. Who are you?
我叫罗妮. 罗妮.拉帕罗罗
Oh,I'm Ronni. Ronni Rapalono.
那个情妇
The mistress?
-请进 -谢谢
-Come on in. -Thanks.
我叫瑞秋.浴室在那儿
I'm Rachel. Bathroom's there.
罗妮,钱德进浴室多久了?
Ronni,how long has Chandler been in the shower?
约5分钟
Oh,like five minutes.
太好了
Perfect.
请系好安全带,“小弟弟”时间到了
Fasten your seat belts,it's pee-pee time.
-崔先生 -早安，亲爱的
-Hey,Mr. Trib. -Hey,good morning,dear.
钱德,该我看你的小弟弟了
Chandler Bing,it's time to see your thing.
-你是怎么搞的?  -我以为你是钱德
-What's with you? -I thought it was Chandler!
你应该在浴室 这样我才能看见你的小弟弟
You were supposed to be in there so I'd see your thing!
抱歉,我的小弟弟和我在那儿
Sorry,my thing was in there with me.
-如何? -不错
-How's it going? -Good.
罗杰想邀大家一起吃晚餐
Roger's having a dinner thing. He wanted me to invite you guys.
-怎么了? -没事
-So,what's going on? -Nothing.
只是…
It's just....
罗杰,我说不上来
It's Roger,you know?
有些事…
There's something about
基本上我们认为他…
We just feel that he's....
-我们讨厌他… -我们讨厌他…
-We hate that guy! -We hate him!
-菲比,我们很抱歉 -很好
-We're sorry,Pheebs. -Okay.
是不是他观察入微
Don't you think it's just that he's so perceptive...
反而吓到你们了
...it freaked you out?
不,我们讨厌他…
No,we hate him!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
-妈,你来干什么? -我拿这个来给你,还有这个
-Ma! What are you doing here? -I came to give you this and this!
好大的戒指!
Big ring!
你为什么要对你爸讲一大堆
Why'd you fill your father's head with garbage...
关于改正的废话呢?
...about making things right?
何不顺其自然呢?
Things were fine this way!
里面有鸡肉,拿去放好
There's chicken in there. Put it away.
拜托,乔依,真的
For God's sake,Joey! Really.
-慢着,你都知道? -我当然知道,你认为呢?
-Hold on. You knew? -Of course I knew. What do you think?
你爸又不是詹姆士邦德（007）
Your father is no James Bond.
你应该听过他的谎言
You should've heard his stories.
“我在会计这儿睡”
"I'm sleeping over at my accountant's."
-那是什么?拜托 -你怎能…
-What is that? Please! -So then,how could you?
记得你爸以前的模样吗?
Do you remember how your father used to be?
总是大吼大叫,总是不开心
Always yelling. Nothing made him happy.
连木材店和瓶内的小船也无法让他开心
Not that wood shop,not those stupid little ships in the bottle.
现在他很开心,这样很好，他总算有个嗜好
Now he's happy. I mean,it's nice. He has a hobby.
妈,恕我直言
Ma,I don't mean to be disrespectful...
你到底在说什么?
... but what the hell are you talking about?
-我是说,你怎么样? -我很好啊
-I mean,what about you? -Me? I'm fine.
在理想的世界中
Look,honey,in an ideal world...
既没有她,而且你爸也长得和斯汀（摇滚歌手）一样帅
...there'd be no her and your father would look like Sting.
还有
And something else:
自从那个“卷毛狗”出现后
Ever since that poodle-stuffer came along...
他感到内疚而开始对我体贴
... he's so ashamed of himself that he's been more attentive.
每天都像我们的结婚纪念日
He's been more loving. It's like every day is our anniversary.
-我该为你高兴? -不需要
-I'm happy for you? -Well,don't be!
因为现在全搞砸了
Now everything's screwed up.
我只想回到从前
I just want it the way it was.
妈,对不起
Ma,I'm sorry.
我自以为做了你想做的事
I just did what I thought you'd want.
我知道,亲爱的,我知道
I know you did,cookie. I know you did.
告诉我,你看见她没?
So tell me. Did you see her?
看到了
Yeah.
-你比她漂亮十倍都不止 -嘴巴真甜
-You're 10 times prettier than she is. -That's sweet.
我斗得过她?
Could I take her?
你有戒指,她斗不过的
With this ring,no contest.
哦,不!永远不要这样做!
Oh,no! Don't ever do that!
-什么? -对不起
-What? -I'm sorry.
我的意思是,你永远不要这么做
I have a thing,which means you can't ever do that!
-怎么了? -没事
-What's wrong,sweetie? -Nothing.
-到底怎么了?快说嘛 -好吧
-No,what's wrong? Come on. -Okay.
我没事 问题出在我朋友身上
It's nothing. I'm fine. It's just It's my friends.
他们对你有意见
They have a liking problem with you...
他们…
...in that they don't.
他们?
They don't?
他们看不见你的好处
But they don't see all the wonderfulness that I see.
他们看不见你好的一面
They don't see all the good and sweet stuff.
-他们认为你有点… -什么?
-They think you're a little -What?
紧张和令人发毛
Intense and creepy.
-哦 -但我菲比不这么认为
-Oh. -But I don't. Me,Phoebe.
-我对他们的反应毫不感到惊讶. -这就是我欣赏你的地方
-I'm not at all surprised about that. -That's why you're so great.
当群体动力失调时
It's quite typical behavior...
这是很平常的反应
...when you have this kind of dysfunctional group dynamic.
这种相互依赖,情绪激动
You know,this kind of codependent,emotionally stunted...
坐在那家烂咖啡屋,拿着又大又蠢的咖啡杯
...sitting in your stupid coffeehouse,with your stupid big cups...
或许还有乳头在上面
...which might as well have nipples on them.
你们都会说“定义我这个人”
And you're all like,"Oh,define me! Define me!
爱我,我需要爱
Love me! I need love!
你和你爸谈过了?
You talked to your dad?
他要以我妈希望的方式继续欺骗我妈
He's gonna keep cheating on Ma like she wanted.
我妈要继续假装她一无所知
Ma will keep pretending she doesn't know.
我妹蒂娜不能再见她丈夫
And my sister,Tina,can't see her husband.
因为他接到禁制令
He got a restraining order.
这两件事没关系,但我今天才听说
Which has nothing to do with it. I found out today.
沃顿山（电视剧的名字）发生了很多变故啊
Things have changed here on Waltons'mountain.
-乔伊,你没事吧? -或许吧
-So,Joey,are you okay? -Yeah,I guess.
他们是…父母
It's just You know,they're parents.
你不得不顺其自然,即使你知道这样做不对
After a certain point,you gotta let go.
但你还是得让他们犯自己的错误
You gotta let them make their own mistakes.
而且几年后我们就和他们一样
And think,in a few years,we'll turn into them.
拜托
Oh,please.
如果我像他们一样 我不是变成追逐金发帅哥的酒鬼
If I turn into my parents,I'll be an alcoholic blond chasing men...
就是变得和我妈一样
...or I'll end up like my mom!
-嗨 -嗨.菲比
-Hey. -Hey,Pheebs.
怎么样?
How's it going?
还好,只是我和罗杰分手了
Okay,except I broke up with Roger.
-没错 -不…真的
-Yeah,right. -No,no,really.
-怎么了? -我说不上来
-What happened? -I don't know. I mean...
他是个好人而且对我很体贴
... he's a good person,and he can be really sweet.
他的某些方面很适合我
In some ways,I think he is so right for me.
只是…我讨厌这个人
It's just.... I hate that guy!
嗨,乔伊.怎么了?
Hi,Joey. What's going on?
为胸脯债务清理跑道
Clear the tracks for the boobie payback.
下一站,瑞秋格林
Next stop,Rachel Greene.
乔伊,你在干什么?
Joey,what the hell were you doing?
对不起,错误的胸脯!
Sorry,wrong boobies!
乔伊!
Hello,Joey!
亲爱的!
Hello,dear!